Hello.
You watched the surveillance cam?
Not yet. I… I'll check it.
All four dressed the same.
All in black jackets, black pants,
and black masks on their faces.
And they were all huge.
What do you mean when you say huge?
How big were they?
All four of them seemed to be
much bigger than both of us, for sure.
And two of them
could easily have been 6'2", or taller.
They all looked like
they worked out a lot.
And some knew karate.
And they had big batons
which had Tasers on them.
Also, they had shoe covers on their feet.
Otherwise, have you noticed
anything out of the ordinary?
Actually…
Mm. Go for it.
You see, some strangers came to our place
three days ago.
They were like, Gun-woo had to join
this professional boxing league they have.
IKFC was the name of the league.
It was a threat, not an invitation.
Those two men were massive.
They even brought us
a billion won to sign.
A billion?
They brought it.
So you believe this case
is related to that?
I do, and I think they'd visit us again.
I checked the security footage
and there's nothing suspicious.
Huh?
Just a few days ago we hooked that up.
You shouldn't listen to our conversation.
Yeah, well, I could hear you.
You were pretty loud.
Sorry about that.
Anyway, the screen doesn't show anything,
and the time doesn't pause at all.
Thanks. You can leave.
Anything else to share?
Oh yeah. He fought
in the WBC Championship last week.
-His opponent was--
-Oh yeah. The boxer. I knew it.
-Uh… yeah.
-Wow!
-I'm honored.
-Thanks.
I used to be a boxer when I was younger.
I watched your fight probably three times.
Oh. Oh, I'm sorry.
Okay then, please go on.
I read that the other fighter
has gone missing.
That's weird, don't you think?
So that might be linked.
That'll do for now.
Me and the team
will start investigating right away.
Your house could be dangerous right now,
so consider moving to another place.
Tell me, in your expert opinion,
is a hotel safe enough for us?
Avoid unknown people and places.
Where should we go then?
Tae-yeong's?
Hey, officer.
-How's it going?
-Hello.
-Hello, detective.
Right here is where the fire began.
You see that melted gasoline container?
An improvised explosive device.
The detonator was likely triggered
by a cell phone signal.
Hmm. And, uh, how knowledgeable
does someone have to be to make this?
Hmm, a high-level EOD tech
should be able to do this.
-Also, we found a wallet in the car.
-Oh!
You have a…
-Right here, detective.
-Ah.
PEOPLE GUARD SECURITY
MANAGER / BODYGUARD SON JIN-NAM
BLOODHOUNDS 2
-Thank you.
-Of course.
Hey, Ma.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm okay if both of you boys are okay.
We're okay for now, Mom.
They told us
two more days for new windows.
That's fine. We can do this.
We must stick together
through all of this.
Mm.
They're moving.
Take a right.
You sure they're coming here?
Yeah.
2196!
-2196!
-We need help over here!
-2196! Hey, hey!
-It's an emergency!
-How long has he been unconscious?
-About ten minutes.
Got it.
Why stop here? This place is abandoned.
Ow! Shit!
Just a minute!
-Well, hello! Welcome.
-Tae-yeong.
This way. Careful. Welcome.
I'm sorry to intrude.
Don't feel bad. I think of all those
wonderful dishes you prepared for me.
This is my honor.
I'm just glad that I can be of assistance.
Sorry about the short notice.
Thank you. Really.
It's nothing. My pleasure.
So you both can stay in this room.
I'll get you some blankets.
Ms. Yoon, follow me.
And this will be your room.
My sister is in the States right now,
and she's almost never here.
It's perfect.
-Tae-yeong.
-Coming!
I need a favor from you.
Can you help me with some research?
Yeah.
NO RESULTS FOUND FOR "IKFC"
The dark web will know.
Dark web? What's that?
It's, uh…
The internet we know
is just the tip of the iceberg,
and far beneath that surface
is what is known as the dark web.
On the dark web, everyone is anonymous,
and criminals gather there
and take advantage of that anonymity.
So, um, I'm not sure what you mean.
How can you stay anonymous?
Uh, so when we're online,
we leave an IP address behind,
which is digital proof.
When crimes occur online,
we can track the IP address
to figure out the criminal's identity.
See, on the dark web,
the IP address is encrypted,
and that's difficult to undo,
so it's nearly impossible
to track the user.
Criminals take advantage
and form a black market,
using Bitcoin to make their transactions.
Whoa. So much information.
Uh…
When we first met,
I worked the cyber investigation unit,
searching for these dark websites
so we can shut them down.
These sites I killed
ran a variety of illegal businesses.
There were some smuggling drugs,
selling IEDs and poisonous substances.
And some sites offered murder for hire.
What shocked me the most was that one site
offered options on how to murder someone.
Options like how to torture,
which acids are better,
staging a suicide, stuff like that.
I still remember
the admin's handle. "M-A-N-J-I."
That's "manji," the spelling
of the Buddhist symbol "man" in English.
Isn't that ironic?
Someone who kills for money
using that name.
So I'm guessing I'll have more luck there.
Here we are.
IKFC.
How does the skin tear so easily?
What's the matter?
What? What?
Uh, well, it requires a credit card,
but you should never
enter your credit card on the dark web.
Anyone there might steal
and use that information.
Do you think you can hack in,
or something like that?
Oh. If I do that,
the admins of the site are able to see me,
and if they're faster than me,
they can hack this computer
before I can break in here.
They could plant a virus
and take full control of this computer.
There are hackers here,
hanging out on the dark web,
who far surpass all my skills.
-Sorry about that.
-No. No worries. Huh.
So… we need a plan.
Oh yeah. A plan.
So we just have to avoid
using our own cards. Isn't that right?
Oh, well, that'll work, for sure.
Woo-jin…
what if we ask our Marine superior?
Mr. Moon Gwang-mu?
Wait a minute. A mule card?
Is that what you're thinking?
Mule cards are created
by stealing identities.
Whoever owns the card
would definitely be in trouble.
What about a dead person?
Uh,
well, if you do that,
then you can't tell me.
Yeah.
Hey.
Yeah?
I'm thinking you stay behind and take care
of Tae-yeong and your mother.
-What? Why?
-Who knows what'll happen?
Okay? I'll meet up
with our old Marine superior.
Mm. I got it.
He's moving now.
Who? Gun-woo?
No. The other guy.
In-beom, hello.
Hi. I'm responsible
for getting you out of prison.
Thanks for accepting my offer.
From now on,
we work together to kill Kim Gun-woo.
I'm confused. Didn't you accept the offer?
You're placing me in a tough position.
Hey.
Listen carefully.
There's absolutely nothing
within ten kilometers of here.
So if you leave this place,
I'll call the police.
The police will likely show up
in ten minutes.
You might be fast,
but I doubt you can sprint 10K that fast.
I can drive a car.
And where are you going, tough guy?
Well? Stupid son of a bitch!
Oh!
Fuck you!
You're going down, asshole!
Come here, fucker!
Hey! Hey! I got you now!
Fucking bastards! You fuckers!
Ah!
Okay, motherfuckers, who's next?!
They're all idiots.
You weak fucking bastards.
Get the fuck up!
Right now!
Get on your feet!
Go for it. I'll kill you.
Ugh, that's fucking great.
Hey.
I thought this little bitch was weak,
but he isn't.
But you did learn how to box
the wrong way.
I'm gonna make cash off Kim Gun-woo.
You can earn some too.
You understand?
Choke on this one.
Ten… Hut!
Ten… hut!
At ease.
-At ease.
-1216 Class Marine Hong Woo-Jin.
Ack!
This Marine is extremely proud
of our fellow junior Marines.
Not because of the boxing title shot!
Before Gun-woo became the champ,
our junior Marines remained strong
and stuck together,
which shows the true Marine spirit.
It's the process
that I'm proudest of. Understand?
Ack!
Now, come here!
So great to see you. How's it been?
Wow, your face looks like
it's seen too much action.
You punk.
-They came up to your home?
-Yes.
Oh. Shit, their intel
is far superior to our military.
They brought a billion won
just for signing.
-One billion?
-Yes.
They offered 15 billion
if he only fought just one time.
Just one fight.
Wow, 15 billion won for one fight.
For that huge price,
I assume it can't only be here in Korea.
That's right. The site says there are
over four million members worldwide.
Four million members? How do they air it?
Well, sir, it's on the dark web now.
Let me explain.
So the Internet that we use, it's, uh…
-It's like the tip of an iceberg--
-Yeah, I know it. Mm.
All right. Dark web.
Honestly, I only
found out about it just now.
Okay, so they show all of these matches
on the dark web.
And the viewers bet on the fights, right?
That seems right.
So… if they can get
a real champion like Gun-woo…
Oh yeah.
I'm sure that underground boxing world
would be a massive powerhouse
in all sports.
And why?
Because just our boy alone
would hold up this league.
Doesn't matter if it's a billion
or 15 billion won.
They'd invest a ton of money, knowing
that in the long run, it'll only grow.
I hear you.
So…
What kind of help
can I bring to the table?
To access their website,
you need to sign up for a membership.
It's the only way.
And you sign up with a credit card only.
That means personal information
can be leaked--
A mule card is a must for this.
You're one step ahead of us
all of the time.
-Sun-bo, hey!
-Yes?
Uh, could you
bring over to me three mule cards?
-Yes.
-Those fancy elite ones.
Yes.
That's that.
Have some more coffee.
Great.
Here. Use them freely.
It's much appreciated, sir.
And who's helping you
with all this right now then?
Good question. For now,
Gun-woo and I are all by ourselves.
Oh. Oh, come on.
If they're as big as I think,
then you both are going to be outmanned.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Sure, it's difficult.
But after beating Kim Myeong-gil,
we're much stronger.
I'm not so sure
that you two are that much stronger.
It seems obvious to me.
Why not ask me to come along and help?
Sir, we thought about that.
And we'd be uncomfortable.
It's way more trouble
for you and your team this time.
Are you still Marine Hong Woo-jin?
Yes, I'm still Marine Hong Woo-jin, sir.
Did you forget?
A blow to one Marine
is a blow to all Marines.
Right? I can't sit around and do nothing
while you boys are in trouble.
What would President Choi in heaven
think of me?
I would be a big disgrace.
That's not how I was trained.
Being a superior has responsibilities.
Two is better than only one.
Add one more…
Three is better, right?
Take it.
Your superior
is on board with you.
No flinching! You've still got it.
Wait. You came by yourself?
Yes. Gun-woo's with his mother.
Ah. You silly, naive boy.
Did anyone follow you here?
-I don't believe this!
-Oh. Right.
They came to your house to find you.
Think they'd stop at that?
-That your car?
-Yes.
New plan.
Drive around the neighborhood,
and after a few blocks, come back around.
Let's find out
what we're up against. Copy that?
He's back.
-Sun-bo.
-Yes?
Get a pen.
Yes.
One, four, three, nine,
two, two, nine, zero.
Weren't we just here?
No.
One, four, three nine. Right?
-The Hyundai.
-Yes.
Where to now?
Woo-jin. Don't look back.
I want you to keep going.
Where else have you been today?
So first we were
at Gun-woo's mother's house.
Now Tae-yeong's place.
First, call Gun-woo. Get him
to take his mother somewhere new.
We don't know
when these thugs might return.
I'm gonna text you an address.
See if they'll follow you there.
Then we can beat 'em up.
WOO-JIN
-Oh, hey.
-Listen carefully.
You have to move calmly and quickly.
Mm-hmm.
You must get Tae-yeong and your mother
out of that place right now.
Why?
Because we're being followed.
You need to take Tae-yeong with you.
Because of us, she's in trouble too.
Mm. Mm. Got it.
What's up with you now?
Mr. Moon and I will find the bastard
who's been harassing and following us.
Keep your mother safe, okay?
And Tae-yeong too.
Mm. Okay.
And where should we go now?
So there's Min-beom. Our best choice.
I can't think of anyone else right now.
We need to act fast.
Mm. On it.
Good. Be careful.
MIN-BEOM
The person
you are trying to reach is unavailable.
Hmm.
Tae-yeong.
So I'm really, really sorry about this.
It turns out that we've put you in danger.
It seems like the men after us
followed us here as well.
Oh.
So it's dangerous for me here too?
Yeah.
They could be here any minute.
I'll pack now.
-I'm really sorry.
-It's okay.
So where are we going now?
Uh, well…
Gun-woo, it's okay.
I'll find us a place to move.
Hello?
Gun-woo? Hello, this is Cho Won-yeong.
I'm President Hong's assistant.
Oh! Yes, hi there.
Unfortunately, President Hong is
in an important meeting
with dignitaries from overseas.
But he asked me to phone you right away.
What message can I pass on?
It's a very private matter.
Whatever you say will remain private.
I promise that.
My loved ones
are in big trouble.
My mother
really needs a safe place
to stay right now.
You can bring your mother
right away to our building, Mr. Kim.
We'll make sure to have guards on standby.
Is there anything else I can do for you?
Okay. Well, actually…
So if it's at all possible,
a motor… motorcycle would help.
I have to save Woo-jin, and traffic
at this time makes that harder.
We can do that.
Any particular type of motorcycle?
Uh, a fast one.
It doesn't matter. I can ride anything.
Then you'll have
the fastest one at our disposal.
I appreciate it.
-Tell me what's up.
-Yeah…
What?
-They're on the run.
-What?
They're all moving out right now.
Who is?
Gun-woo, his mom,
and that chick in the wheelchair.
What do we do?
What?
Sir, I'm bringing in Hong Woo-jin,
not his mom. Okay?
-Yeah so?
-I need backup and a location.
Send help his way.
Of course.
Welcome.
Thanks, hello. I so appreciate
you looking after Tae-yeong and my mother.
-Give them a hand.
-Yes, of course.
-You have that motorcycle?
-It's right over there.
-Will this work?
-Yeah.
WOO-JIN
Be careful.
I will.
Where are you, Woo-jin?
I'm at an intersection near a school.
Waiting for the light to change.
The auto shop is just after the light.
Got it. On my way now.
LEE DONG-HYEON
MANAGER
Yeah.
There's a factory five minutes away
from you. It's remote and very quiet.
Send the address.
Here it comes.
And we're sending reinforcements.
That crazy fucker!
What the fuck is happening?
This stupid motherfucker just took off.
I'll send a new address.
Was it you, you fucker?
Ah, shit.
Let go of me!
Hey, let go!
Let go!
Ah!
No, wait, don't! Oh shit.
Sir! You okay?
Do I look okay?
I have a massive hole in my head.
No, it's not so bad.
-It's like an open faucet.
-A Marine's blood is sweat.
A Marine's blood is…
Shut the fuck up, man.
Ack!
Uh, sir…
That's enough of their bullshit.
Woo-jin!
What is it? Drop it, you bastard!
Damn it. Let go!
You fucker!
Oh!
I told you to shut up.
Sir, come on!
Hey!
Ah!
Okay.
You okay?
Yes. Except for my left hand.
No. You're fine. You told me
that a Marine's blood is sweat.
A reservist's blood… is blood only.
-Let's get this asshole in the car.
-Of course.
-Wait.
-What?
Who is that?
What's up now?
I don't think
they're here to congratulate us.
-Mr. Moon.
-Yeah?
We should leave.
-Hey! Stop! Catch those fuckers!
-Get over there!
-Go, go, go, go!
-You're dead, you hear me?
This way!
This way. Let's go up!
Don't let them get away!
-Oh fuck!
-Get him!
Go! Hurry up! Let's go!
Get him until he talks!
Now go, go, go!
Son of a bitch!
Come on!
Woo-jin, I got this. You go ahead!
Ack!
Get him!
Fuck you, you fucking asshole!
Shit.
-Get up there.
-He's getting away!
-Don't let him get away!
-Oh, fuck. Fuck!
-Go, go, go! Move!
-Go, go, go!
Oh man.
We got him.
Ow, fuck! Block it!
-Why won't you die?
-It's all over.
Ah, shit! Come and get me!
Move! Go around!
Oh, fuck. They're not wasting any time.
Oh, shit.
-You're fucking dead!
-I can't wait to fucking kill you.
Just keep on running.
-You're fucking mine!
-Hey, you son of a bitch!
Oh shit!
-Whoa!
-What are you gonna do?
Huh? What the fuck
are you doing falling over?
Stupid idiot.
-Hey, you go.
-I got it.
-Who's next?
-Go!
See you back here!
Let's go!
Get at him!
-Come on!
-Get his head!
Come on!
Good! Get him!
Come on, let's go!
-Come on! You like that? Fucker.
-Stay down!
Take that!
I got the face.
Ah! Ah!
Oh God, that fucking hurts!
Shit.
-Fuck that.
-Who the hell is that guy?
-What are you looking at?
-Wanna end up like this?
-Ow, my fucking back.
-Get out of here, boy. Bitch.
-Huh?
-Fucking pipe.
Fucking idiot.
Nerve of this guy.
Huh. Who the fuck are you?
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Let's go, pretty boy.
Pretty motherfucker, let's go.
Yeah, bring it.
Come on. Get him!
You can't take all of us. Stop this.
What the fuck?
Son of a bitch!
Fucking bastard!
Take this!
You motherfucker.
Ah!
Wow, you really know how to fight.
Gun-woo.
Gun-woo!
Hey, listen!
Woo-jin!
You okay?
It's all good.
Wow.
Shit, that looks bad.
Yeah?
A Marine needs help.
Oh.
Sir!
-I'm okay.
-Yeah?
We should leave here.
Yeah.
Let's go.
What was that?